intrasight.net 2016-03-24

# Zeta Interactive

## Privacy Policy

Zeta Interactive is a leading provider of e–mail based marketing services and solutions. This Privacy Policy (also referred to herein as our “Policy”) has been created by Zeta Interactive as part of our commitment to data protection and privacy. Because you may provide us with personal information, we have developed this Policy to inform you of Zeta Interactive’s practices concerning such information. If you have additional questions about this Policy, please feel free to [email us.](mailto:info@zetainteractive.com?subject=Privacy)

**What Personal Information Does Zeta Interactive Collect?**

Zeta Interactive uses the information it collects to improve your experience with Zeta Interactive, including personalizing and enhancing the experience we provide to you on our web site. The types of information we may collect about you include:

  * Information You Give Us. We receive and store any information you enter on our web site and contact page, through registration and other forms, or give us in any other way. This may include you name, the company you work for, postal address, email address, telephone number, marketing preferences, and other information.
  * Information from Other Sources. We may receive information about you from other sources. If you provide information to Zeta Interactive, we may collect additional information about you, including information about you from Zeta Interactive affiliates and other sources. For more information, read about Fair Information Practices below.
  * Automatic Information: We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with our web sites. For example, like many web sites, we use “cookies,” and we obtain certain types of information when your web browser accesses our web sites. This may include individual and aggregate visitor preferences and session information, as well as information such as your IP address and the browser you are using. Our use of cookies is described in greater detail in the following section.

If you become a customer of our service, we may send you service–related announcements on occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email. Generally, you may not opt out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account.

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one–time email inviting him or her to visit the site. Zeta Interactive stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one–time email and tracking the success of our referral program.

Zeta Interactive may also send you newsletters from time to time to update you with news and current events about our company. If you do not wish to receive these emails, you will have an opportunity to opt-out

Your friend may contact us at [info@zetainteractive.com](mailto:info@zetainteractive.com?subject=Privacy) to request that we remove this information from our database.

**What Are Cookies and How Does Zeta Interactive Use Them?**

A cookie is a text–only string of information that a web site transfers to the cookie file of the browser on your computer’s hard disk so that the website can remember who you are. A cookie will typically contain the name of the domain from which the cookie has come, the “lifetime” of the cookie, and a value, usually a randomly generated unique number. Many cookies last only through a single session, or visit. Others may have an expiration date, or may remain on your computer until you delete them. Cookies can help a web site to arrange content to match your preferred interests more quickly and also to improve the user experience. Most major web sites use cookies.

Web beacons may be used to monitor web site traffic in conjunction with cookies. A web beacon is a graphic on a web page or in an email message designed to track pages viewed and messages opened. Web beacons are often invisible because they are typically only 1–pixel by 1–pixel in size. We may place Web beacons on our web pages to collect data about visitors. When a user requests a Zeta Interactive web page, a web beacon may be retrieved/activated. Once the Web beacon is retrieved/activated, it points to an external site to retrieve the image. At that time it can also pass along information such as the IP address of the computer that retrieved the image, the time the Web beacon was viewed and for how long, and the type of browser that retrieved the image. This information can then be compiled and made available to Zeta Interactive. Web beacons, along with cookies, enable us to enhance your experience on the Zeta Interactive site. Turning off the browser’s cookies will prevent web beacons from tracking your specific activity. The web beacon may still record an anonymous visit from your IP address, but personal information will not be recorded (information on how to “turn off” cookies provided below).

**How Does Zeta Interactive Use Cookies?**  
We use cookies for a number of purposes–for example, to maintain continuity during a user session, to gather data about the usage of our web site for research and other purposes, to store your preferences for certain kinds of information and marketing offers, or to store a username or encrypted customer identification number so that you do not have to provide this information every time you return to our site. Our cookies are not used to gather personally identifiable information.  
How Can I Prevent the Use of Cookies? You can decide if and how your computer will accept a cookie by configuring your preferences or options in your browser. The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable or delete cookies altogether. However, please note that if you choose to reject cookies, you may not be able to use certain online services or web site features.

**Does Zeta Interactive Share the Information It Receives?**

Zeta Interactive does not rent, loan, trade or lease any personal information without prior consent.

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our web site.

**What Choices Do I Have?**

Zeta Interactive maintains an email marketing newsletter list to communicate with our clients and prospects. We do not rent, loan, trade or lease the addresses on our list to anyone. All email messages sent to this list include an opportunity to unsubscribe or opt–out of receiving future Insight newsletters.

Zeta Interactive maintains a postal mailing list to communicate with our clients and prospects. We do not rent, loan, trade or lease our list to anyone. You can request to be removed from our mailing list by contacting us via email. You may also request to be removed from our mailing list at the postal address below:

**Zeta Interactive**  
185 Madison Ave, 5th Floor,  
New York, NY 10016  
T: 212-967-5055  
F: 212.967-1028  
Email: [info@zetainteractive.com](mailto:info@zetainteractive.com?subject=Privacy)

**Can I Access & Correct My Personal Information?**

If you would like to update your information please go to the Contact Us window and submit a new form with updated contact information. Any Profile updates or changes will take place within a 24–hour period.

To request access to the information we have about you, please send a request via email. Zeta Interactive will respond within 30 days.

**How Is Information About Me Kept Secure?**  
We protect information we collect about you by maintaining physical, electronic and procedural safeguards. All information is secure and may be accessed only by key staff members of Zeta Interactive. Zeta Interactive does not request sensitive information (such as a credit card number and/or social security number). We take every precaution to protect your information both online and offline. Periodically, our employees are notified about the importance we place on privacy and security, and what they can do to ensure our clients’ information is protected. The servers on which we store data are kept in a secure environment. If you have any questions about security, click here to send an email.

**How Will I Know About Changes to This Policy?**  
Zeta Interactive may revise this Policy from time to time. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this Privacy Policy and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, or by means of a notice on our home page. You should bookmark and periodically review this page to ensure that you are familiar with the most current version of this Policy. You can determine when this Policy was last revised by checking the "Last Revised" legend at the top of the Policy.

###  Additional Privacy Information

**How Does Zeta Interactive Protect the Privacy of Information It Collects and Manages on Behalf of Its Clients?**

Zeta Interactive works with the world's leading marketers (our clients) to develop direct mail and permission-based email marketing communications to send to their customers (client’s customers/consumers).

Zeta Interactive’s role in supporting our clients may include hosting client data, compiling or procuring prospect/acquisition data for our clients, delivery of direct mail or email, tracking results of direct mail or email campaigns, analysis of data, hosting of response data collection sites, and transferring collected data back to our clients or to an Zeta Interactive hosted database.

Zeta Interactive treats all client customer data as confidential. Zeta Interactive is contractually bound to keep our clients' customer data private and this data is never shared across clients or with any third party that is not authorized by a client to receive its customer data. Zeta Interactive only uses its clients’ customer data for the specific purpose of providing services to its clients as authorized by our clients. It is our client’s responsibility (as a user of our products and services) to provide proper notice to its customers/consumers with regard to any required notices as to its data collection and data use practices, including any email or internet tracking devices.

Zeta Interactive may, however, share our clients’ customer data with a Zeta Interactive affiliate company or another company if such sharing is in connection with providing services to our clients, or in relation to a sale or consolidation of Zeta Interactive’s assets, provided, however, that all such companies agree to honor all of the privacy commitments set forth in this Policy and have demonstrated appropriate levels of their ability to so protect the privacy of our clients’ data.

Some of our clients independently use Zeta Interactive's technology platforms to design and send their direct mail or email campaigns without the involvement Zeta Interactive support staff. Zeta Interactive informs all of its clients in writing about its stringent Policy against sending unsolicited commercial email, or sending direct mail in a manner not consistent with Direct Marketing Association (DMA) guidelines. If Zeta Interactive determines that a client has knowingly used its systems for sending unsolicited commercial email, or direct mail in a manner inconsistent with DMA guidelines, it may revoke the client's permission to send direct mail or email using our products or our systems.

###  US-EU Safe Harbor

Zeta Interactive complies with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries. Zeta Interactive has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view Zeta Interactive’s certification, please visit <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>

###  Contact Information

If you have a privacy issue that needs addressing, you may contact us via email at [info@zetainteractive.com](mailto:info@zetainteractive.com?subject=Privacy), or at the postal address below. You may also contact TRUSTe, our dispute resolution partner, by clicking [here](http://www.truste.com/about-TRUSTe/contact-us).

Zeta Interactive  
185 Madison Ave, 5th Floor,  
New York, NY 10016  
T: 212-967-5055  
F: 212-967.1028  
Email: [info@zetainteractive.com](mailto:info@zetainteractive.com)

###  Dispute Resolution

Zeta Interactive's participates in the U.S. - E.U. Safe Harbor framework as set forth by the United States Department of Commerce. As part of our [participation](http://export.gov/safeharbor/) in the safe harbor, we have agreed to TRUSTe dispute resolution for disputes relating to our compliance with the Safe Harbor Privacy Framework. Please click [here](http://www.truste.com/about-TRUSTe/contact-us) for fax and postal mail information. TRUSTe's Dispute Resolution process is only available in English.

###  Fair Information Practices

Zeta Interactive, or it subsidiaries, may collect data off–line directly from consumers or from other data collection sources in order to compile acquisition lists of various consumers who may be interested in receiving marketing materials from Zeta Interactive clients. Zeta Interactive respects and promotes consumer privacy and is committed to maintaining the balance between the legitimate information needs of businesses and the concerns of individuals and the public at large about fair information practices. In its consumer data collection practices, Zeta Interactive and all business with whom Zeta Interactive associates, employ the following fair information practices.

**Fair Information practices used by Zeta Interactive and its data providers:**

  * Collection of relevant and socially legitimate information from reputable sources
  * Taking reasonable steps to assure the accuracy of information, including permitting individuals to correct inaccuracies or inform the source of the correct information. Safeguarding information by restricting access to only those who have a legitimate need and right to access the information.
  * Taking reasonable steps to protect against the misuse of non-public information
  * Informing customers of how information is used.
  * Maintaining systems to protect information from unauthorized access, including using industry standard secure socket layer (“SSL”) encryption when transmitting sensitive information over the public Internet.
  * Educating employees on the importance of privacy issues and requirements.
  * Links to Other Web Sites.

This web site contains links to other sites. The inclusion of any link does not imply our endorsement of the external site company, its web site, or the products and services it promotes and sells. Please be aware that Zeta Interactive is not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by Zeta Interactive.
